<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sean Porter</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Sean Porter</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 12:46:22 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3D Printer</title><link>/posts/ender3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 12:46:22 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/ender3/</guid><description>Ender 3 + New Shelf I finally picked up a 3d printer! I ignored their progress for a few years &amp;amp; now some entry level models like this Ender 3 are fairly affordable.
As is tradition, the first thing I did with it was use an arduino uno &amp;amp; get a bootloader + aftermarket firmare flashed onto the controller (Marlin, for anyone interested). The default firmware doesn&amp;rsquo;t have thermal runaway protection so this should make it a bit safer.</description></item><item><title>Config - Be Explicit</title><link>/posts/ansible-cfg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 15:38:59 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/ansible-cfg/</guid><description>The Motivation: We rely on ansible for some deploys &amp;amp; to enforce certain state at our retail locations; I was burned by an upgrade to this system last week and thought it would be nice to talk about what happened and what could have been done to prevent it.
The Incident: I built some tooling around automated playbook retries because the connection to some of our hosts is pretty bad (3G levels of bad&amp;hellip;); across ~5500 hosts something is almost guaranteed to fail.</description></item><item><title>The Keyboard Of Many Names</title><link>/posts/helidox/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 11:55:53 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/helidox/</guid><description>The CRKBD, Corne keyboard, Helidox.
my thoughts: I don&amp;rsquo;t know why this thing has so many different names. I do know, however, that it is definitely my current favorite board. Same layout as the Iris but without the top number row. The OLED screens on the side are gimmicky but moving the TRRS jacks &amp;amp; controllers away from the keys allows this to stay much thinner, even without low profile switches.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>Hello! My name is Sean Porter. I am a father, husband, and programmer. I have a general interest in all technology, but especially love seeing how software can improve our lives and disrupt established industries in a way that was never possible before. I make a intentional effort to get better every day.
I write application, CI, and infrastructure code; sometimes I get paged when a service goes down then I fix it so it doesn&amp;rsquo;t.</description></item></channel></rss>